Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
Id have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know...
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
I'll blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As I make foes of the world
Im bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Taste good?
Tastes so good!
Hey, guys!
I found a shaved ice stall over there!
Shaved ice!
I wanna try shaved ice, too!
Let's go, O-Nami-chan!
Mm-hmm!
O-Nami-chan, hurry, hurry!
bos
There're so many flavors!
I can't decide!
I wanna try the oshiruko flavor!
Annoying scum!
I see no end to this!
Momonosuke-kun!
I will lend you aid!
You will not!
But why?!
Why will you not allow me to fight?!
You mustn't!
You must not lay your hand upon him...!
Yamato!
Just bring Straw Hat Luffy
to me already, dammit!
Ninja Art: Scrolling Technique!
Fire Escape!
Burn to ash...
Navy filth!
Just kidding!
Firebreak Forest!
How the hell could I possibly serve
as a Navy Admiral...
...with such an obvious weakness?!
Water's important for
nature and humans...
Ya know?
Unhand me!
Raizo!
Foul beast! Cut as we might,
they keep growing back!
Raizo-san!
Does he-gara have no weakness?!
Do we really gotta cut
all o' them?!
Dog!
Blast-
Momonosuke-kun...
Why?
Stairs?
Oh?
How did you sniff us out here?
You weren't with the others.
Of course I'd find that suspicious.
Don't talk about me like
I'm some hyena.
Do watch your step.
'Tis moldy.
I told neither Kaido
nor Orochi of this route...
But as the All-Star Jack is a Fishman,
they found the Poneglyph in no time.
How would being
a Fishman help find it?
Best to see for oneself.
Just how deep are we going?
Well...
Centuries into the past.
Say, Tengu-san...
What might be
the source of this dim light?
A block of glass is installed there.
Peer through it,
if you so wish.
We have reached the ocean floor.
Room.
Eh?
Now that's unfair!
See anything?
The Land of Wano...
on the seafloor?!
That is the Land of Wano,
eight hundred years ago.
Or rather, what once was.
"Eight hundred years ago"?
What do you mean by that?
'Tis precisely as I say.
But I know not what transpired
to have caused what you see.
And as that is not seawater in which it lies,
it is relatively well-preserved.
This is what I know:4
The Land of Wano was once located
at a base of a great mountain named Fujiyama.
At one point walls were built,
enclosing the island,
causing rainwater to accumulate over time.
People abandoned these
now-uninhabitable towns,
moved up the mountain,
and founded a new country.
And that's the current Land of Wano?
Indeed.
And here we are!
A Road Poneglyph...
This makes three,
I do believe...
If we find the one remaining,
we can reach Laugh Tale.
We tread upon...
...the high ground in a cave
at the foot of Fujiyama.
And what is more, so they say...
...the Ancient Weapon Pluton
lies deeper still!
What?
I have never seen it myself,
not that I could even show it to you now.
To retrieve it requires
dismantling of the walls!
In other words, to "open the borders" would mean
destroying the defensive walls,
and unleashing the Ancient Weapon!
Opening the borders
means unleashing the weapon?
Why would Kozuki Oden
have wanted to do such a thing?
This is the sum of what has been
handed down within the Shogunate.
I know nothing of what
Oden discovered abroad...
Yummy!
Yum, mmm!
Hey, Bepo!
There was a shaved ice stall!
What?! Shaved ice?!
Where?! Where?!
Leave this place at once!
Momonosuke-sama!
Mere humans're no match
for Mother Nature!
Don't ya get it?
If Kaido were here, I wouldn't be!
Hate to admit it,
but Kaido's sheer dominance...
...kept this country's enemies at bay!
If you can understand that much,
you'll bring Straw Hat Luffy to me!
Soon as I lop off his head,
I'm outta here!
Momonosuke-kun!
Let us turn to Luffy and his crew for aid!
They will not lose to this fool!
We cannot do that!
Eh?
And we will not accept aid from you, either!
Do not aid us!
You were imprisoned within Onigashima for so long,
and now you can finally be free!
And so, I will give you
a proper send-off!
For too long have I been dependent upon
Luffy, Zoro, and their allies!
If those of us that remain in this country
cannot drive out our enemies...
If we rely on those
who will be departing...
We will have proven our inability...
...to defend our land in the future!
Momonosuke-kun...
Begone, foul creature of wood!
Why?! Why can I not bring it forth?!
Oh, wow...
He's kinda like a kid.
Who knew there was
such a worthless dragon?
Get out!
I did it!
Momonosuke-sama!
Amazing, 'tis practically as Kaido's...!
Get out!
Get out, and begone from our land!
Dammit...!
Now hold on, dumbass!
Incredible! He has mastered
his dragon form!
Alas, his aim is not the most steady...
Oopsie daisy...
Tryin' to burn down
the whole damn village, huh...
You want a fight,
I'll give ya a fight...
Frickin' Kaido wannabe...
I'm gonna skewer ya,
mouth to tail!
Can't move...
Conqueror's Haki?!
Whose the hell is it?!
Don't tell me...
The Red-Hair Pirates?!
Is that who's there?!
C'mon, Boss!
Ya can't just whip out your Haki like that!
It's too hard on our new crewmates!
I won't tell you it's unfair, Navy dog...
But going after these exhausted "sprouts"
just after they changed pirate history...
...is a bit tasteless, don't you think?
The new era really
scaring you that much?
I'm not here to fight your bunch!
Not yet, anyway!
All right, already!
Marvelous!
You did it, Momonosuke-kun!
You drove him out!
You defended Wano!
I defended Wano?
I defended my country?
You are incredible, Momonosuke-kun!
There he goes!
Good on ya, Momo!
Guess we don't get a turn.
Hell of a Haki that was, though...
Yeah... What was that?
Kinda made me think of
a familiar face...!
Raizo!
Shinobu-san!
You must live!
I can scarcely believe
Raizo and Shinobu wasted away like this...
Most terrifying sorcery, it is.
Frustrating as it is,
he spoke the truth.
Kaido served as a deterrent
against enemies of this nation...
Tis my shame to bear!
My apologies!
I was in Kuri,
and as a result knew nothing of this!
Ain't yer fault,
wasn't much harm done besides.
An' it's all thanks ta
Momonosuke-sama's huge hand in it!
So don'cha worry.
By the way,
how's O-Tsuru-san these days?
Well... Okobore Town
caught fire,
and she suffered horrible burns,
yet she survived...
Oh, O-Tsuru-san!
Yes?
I heard Kin-san came back!
Yes, he has.
He already returned to the capital, though.
You're from the capital, too.
You ought to go back for him!
Aye.
I would much like to be with him, too...
My, my... Even twenty years later,
Tsuru has retained her beauty...
Hey! Dogs like cheese,
but not that much cheese!
Prrmeow meowmeow!
How wonderful, Kin-sama!
What is the matter, Raizo?!
Do you want something?
I want...
What is it?
to be popular, too.
You-gara need to
recuperate first, Raizo!
This is big monkeyin' news!
Found you!
Want shome oden?
Duke Inuarashi and Governor Nekomamushi
are howlin' for you!
There you are, Carrot.
What's up?
You rang,
Duke? Governor Nekomamushi?
We was waitin' for ya.
We were thinking of having you-gara succeed us
as ruler of the Mokomo Dukedom.
Ruler?!
Yaaaay!
'Kay, sure!
Whaaaa?!
The ruler?!
I dun wanna!
There's no way I can handle that!
www
Thing is...
...the cat and I have decided to stay here in Wano,
and as samurai of the Kozuki Clan,
we will protect Momonosuke-sama.
Prrrmeow meowmeow!
You-gara went abroad with Luffy's crew,
somethin' few've done,
so we's sure ya got what it takes
t'lead the next generation.
Wait, hold on!
There're so many others
that're stronger than me, though!
That goes without saying!
To guard the country
is our job!
I'll support you, too. 11
This is what the Duke and the Governor decided.
Carrot! Most of all of us, you-teia carry...
...Pedro's will in your heart.
Pedro...
The rest's up to yous.
Zou's now in
you-gara youngsters' hands!
You speak the truth...?
You are our grandfather?
Mm.
am Oden's father.
So you really were alive!
I am sorry...
I could not bear to
show my face to you two.
I could not save Oden...
...much less could I save our country.
For that, I am sorry...
So sorry...
How I longed to see you!
As did !!
Thank you.
You are the very image of
Oden himself, Momonosuke!
Grandfather!
For us, having lost our parents,
simply knowing we have
living relatives gives us great courage!
I feel the same!
So please, do not apologize!
I was astonished!
So he was Sukiyaki-sama!
Not once did
the thought cross my mind!
My heart leapt into my throat!
I am ever grateful
that he yet lives!
I knew you lot would
certainly take notice...
Who would wear a tengu mask
when there is no festival?
We did not think you
a mere swordsmith.
We felt it would be rude
to draw attention to the fact...
Would you agree, Kin-sama?
Indeed so!
I regret to have had you
treat the issue so...
can impart to you our land's history,
but seeing as I am but a doddering old man,
that is the extent of
what I am able to offer.
I beg of you, do not tell our subjects of me.
Let me live out the rest of my days in peace.
From this point onward,
the new era is yours to shape.
Just the fact that you are alive
gives us strength!
Say whadaa?!
Pluton's in this country?!
Yes. I didn't get to see it, however...
But it's here, for certain!
That thing really exists, huh?
Ain't that the thing Franky
had the blueprints to 'n burned 'em?
That's right.
An Ancient Weapon,
bearing the name of a god:
Pluton.
Do you want it for yourself, Luffy?
Nah, I dun need it.
Thought not
Yet, Oden attempted to unleash it.
Why, I wonder?
What? What?
The bad guys!!
What was that?
Are you likening mature women...
...to devastating weapons?
Who the hellre you
s'posed to be?!
Who am I, you ask?
Do you not recognize me?
A minor incident may have
caused a little emaciation....
...but 'tis I, Shinobu!
Whaaaa?!
That little bit of
emaciation did wonders!
You look so incredible,
I've lost my backbone!
Though I'm all bones to begin with!
Big Bro, Big Bro!
Shinobu-chan took me in
as her apprentice!
I'mma get stronger
so's the next time we meet,
I want ya to lemme join yer crew!
If ya can use
ninja arts by then,
you got it!
Awwright!
I'm gonna put in hard work 'n
become a bewitchin' ninja lady!
Nin, nin!
Oooh, you're such a cutie, O-Tama!
You're the bestest!
I can't believe it...
Pluton's in Wano?
First Poseidon, and now this...
I know someone who'll be
thrilled to hear about this!
Shogun!
There you are!
The regions have submitted their
individual reconstruction plans.
Let us see...
That is the funding estimate.
Mmm. Good work.
Shogun!
Proposals to repurpose
the weapon factory sites have come in.
Mmm... Let us go, then.
Shogun! I humbly request
your opinion on the reservoir later.
We must talk about the
all-region meeting with the Daimyos!
Mmm.
Shogun!
Hey, Zoro!
Might you teach me some
of your sword tech...
...niques...
Luffy? Zoro?
O-Nami! Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopperemon!
Robin! Franky!
Bonekichi! Jinbe!
Yamato!
Where is everyone?!
Anyone?!
Hiyori! Have you seen
Luffy and the others?!
They have departed after
bidding their farewells to everyone...
I'm so sad!
"Bidding their farewells"?
Yet they said
nothing of this to me...
Momonosuke-sama!
Ki-Kin'emon!
Luffy and his crew have...
I have just learned
of this as well!
What?! You, too, Kin'emon?!
I inquired, and Denjiro and the others
have already bade them farewell!
Why did they not
say anything to us!!
Pick another date, Straw Hatter!
Why the hell do I gotta?!
Cause it's weird!
Settin' sail together, I mean!
The alliance is done!
We're enemies now.
My crew decided we'd set off today!
Same here!
You change first, Trafalgar!
How about I not,
and you take your own advice?
I ain't changin', neither!
This is ridiculous...
It's not like we all tried
to pick the same day...
So we're pickin'
separate directions!
The Log Pose locked on
to three directions...
Northeast, east, and southeast!
Choose.
The middle one!
I'm set, then...
BeHeading northeast
will get you the farthest ahead.
Maybe try using your brains once in a while?
Morons.
"The middle one"?
What are you, kids?
That settles my destination.
You two can figure out
the rest on your own, yeah?
Straw Hat, pick one!
One of 'em says "East"
This'n!
got "East"!
I picked the loser!
Sorry, guys!
There's danger no matter
which way, dammit!
Literally nobody cares!
Just help with the cargo, Luffy!
I'm an Emperor of the Sea,
but I lost the raffle!
Cry more,
why don'cha?!
But...
...when it comes to Emperors,
the one who really makes me mad...
...is this guy!
Buggy the Genius Jester!
Hwuuuuh?!
The heck's up with this?!
CROSS
TRUSS
GUILD
Those're Crocodile and
Hawkeye, ain't they?!
Why're they showin' up like
they're under Buggy?!
Nah, there's no way
Hawkeye'd work for him...
If these two men are actually
under his command,
then he's definitely earned the right
to be called an Emperor.
But he's a total dumbass!
What the hell happened?
Seems like this company
called Cross Guild...
...started putting bounties on marines.
The Navy were the hunters this whole time,
...but now they gotta worry about
being hunted by civilians.
While we were holed up
in this isolated country,
the world's changed a ton.
No complaints about
our directions, yeah?
Soon as we sail outta here,
it's back to bein' a free-for-all!
What's this, Trafalgar?
Copy of a Road Poneglyph.
You've earned your right to it,
same as us.
Cheating takes all the fun out of it...
So Kaido did have one, as I thought...
Same kinda thing that we got from
one of Big Mom's generals?
We'd better get serious about this too, Kid!
If we wanna be in the running
for the One Piece...
We need to find
"the Man with the Burn Scar", right?
But we hardly got any leads...
"Burn Scar"?
What's that about?
You don't know, huh?!
Works out for us, then!
What's that?!
Spit it out!
Hey, Yamato!
Where are you?!
Yamato!
Are you not here, either?!
Momonosuke-kun!
I am over here!
Where, though?
Your usual spot on the roof, I take it?
Right, then!
I have decided!
Let us go to where
Luffy and his crew are!
1...
...Shall live as Kozuki Oden did!
"Time's up'
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Raise up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly
er, we can go and